{
  "questions":
  [
    {"question":"How is the 'questions' entry formatted?",
     "answer type":"mc",
     "correct answer":"c",
     "possible answers":["[\"questions\": [...]]",
                         "{\"questions\": {...}}",
                         "{\"questions\": [...]}",
                         "[\"questions\": {...}]"]},

    {"question":"Square brackets indicate objects in JSON and curly brackets indicate lists in JSON.",
     "answer type":"tF",
     "correct answer":"f",
     "possible answers":["w"]},

    {"question":"Which one of these are wrong?",
     "answer type":"mc",
     "correct answer":"B",
     "possible answers":[
                         "{\n     \"questions\":\n     [\n      {\"question\":\"example question?\"\n       \"correct answer\":\"c\"\n       \"answer type\":\"Mc\"\n       \"possible answers\":[\n         \"this answer\",\n         \"or this answer\",\n         \"or even this answer\"]\n      }\n     ]\n    }",

                         "{\n     \"questions\":\n     [\n      {\"question\":\"example question?\"\n       \"correct answer\":\"c\"\n       \"answer type\":\"Mc\"\n       \"Possible answers\":[\n         \"this answer\",\n         \"or this answer\",\n         \"or even this answer\"]\n      }\n     ]\n    }",

                         "{\n     \"questions\":\n     [\n      {\"correct answer\":\"c\"\n       \"answer type\":\"Mc\"\n       \"possible answers\":[\n         \"this answer\",\n         \"or this answer\",\n         \"or even this answer\"]\n       \"question\":\"example question?\"\n      }\n     ]\n    }",

                         "{\n     \"questions\":\n     [\n      {\"answer type\":\"Mc\"\n       \"possible answers\":[\n         \"this answer\",\n         \"or this answer\",\n         \"or even this answer\"]\n       \"question\":\"example question?\"\n       \"correct answer\":\"c\"\n      }\n     ]\n    }"]},

    {"question":"An error would occur if one or none the question entrys doesn't exist.",
     "answer type":"Tf",
     "correct answer":"T",
     "possible answers":["w"]},

    {"question":"JSON doesn't have specific syntax.",
     "answer type":"tf",
     "correct answer":"F",
     "possible answers":["w"]},

    {"question":"What happens if an error occurs?",
     "answer type":"mC",
     "correct answer":"A",
     "possible answers":["The program tells you the error and doesn't allow the user to select the quiz.",
                         "The program crashes.",
                         "The program fixes the error for you.",
                         "The program doesn't do anything."]},

    {"question":"Every question entry contains entries for: question, answer type, correct answer and question number.",
     "answer type":"Tf",
     "correct answer":"f",
     "possible answers":["y"]},

    {"question":"Every question entry contains entries for: question, answer type, correct answer and possible answers.",
     "answer type":"Tf",
     "correct answer":"T",
     "possible answers":["y"]},

    {"question":"These question entries are NOT case sensitive.",
     "answer type":"Tf",
     "correct answer":"F",
     "possible answers":["y"]},

    {"question":"What indicates objects in JSON?",
     "answer type":"MC",
     "correct answer":"d",
     "possible answers":["[]",
                         "()",
                         "<>",
                         "{}"]},

    {"question":"The 'questions' entry is required.",
     "answer type":"tF",
     "correct answer":"T",
     "possible answers":["l"]},

    {"question":"You don't need to put double quotes around entries and values. It's just a suggestion.",
     "answer type":"TF",
     "correct answer":"f",
     "possible answers":["a"]},

    {"question":"JSON stands for Jerry Sells Oxygen in November.",
     "answer type":"tf",
     "correct answer":"F",
     "possible answers":["w"]},

    {"question":"JSON stands for Java Script Object Notation.",
     "answer type":"tf",
     "correct answer":"T",
     "possible answers":["e"]},

    {"question":"What is an example of a list?",
     "answer type":"Mc",
     "correct answer":"c",
     "possible answers":["milk, cheese, eggs, butter",
                         "{milk, cheese, eggs, butter}",
                         "[milk, cheese, eggs, butter]",
                         "milkcheeseeggsbutter"]},
    {"question":"What programming language is this SimQs written in?",
     "answer type":"Mc",
     "correct answer":"e",
     "possible answers":["Java",
                         "Rust",
                         "C++",
                         "C",
                         "Python",
                         "Java Script",
                         "Go",
                         "Assembly",
                         "Scratch",
                         "English"]}
  ]
}
